Hello and welcome to the school's Understanded CAPM NOGs package manager.
My name is Mukden and I will be an instructor during the school's.
In this course, we will answer several important questions, first one, how you can initialize your
project using NPM.
What is the package JSON file?
We will discuss semantic versioning and you will understand what is the difference between major minor
and software versions.
And I'll explain you in which cases, which version should be updated.
You will also understand what special characters such as Steel or Garratt mean when they used along
with package.
I will also answer a very common question why not modules folder is so large and why it shouldn't be
committed to source control systems.
We will talk about difference between dependencies and development dependencies, and you will clearly
understand, in which case you should add baggage as dependency and in which cases as development dependency.
In order to answer this question, we will talk about difference between browser applications and several
packages, and you'll get a challenge to create one of the browser applications yourself and you will
not use any external modules for that.
I will also explain purpose of the package.
This log, the JSON file or in Yoran.
It is young but log.
You'll understand how this files helps you to keep same software packages, viruses on different computers.
But what about and postscripts probably have seen such a long list of scripts in the package.
What is the purpose of each script, how it is used, how it is executed?
In this growth, we will talk about built in a script such as start, start, start, stop, restart
and so on.
We will also discuss KOSTERMAN film scripts and you will create several scripts yourself.
We will also discuss how you can combine different scripts in a one script.
We will discuss the purpose of the DOD Benfold, the load modules folder, and I'll explain to you what
is executable script.
Probably earlier you have seen such a line in the executable script.
And in this course, I'll explain you how it is used on Windows and on Mac.
And this girls, I'll give you several challenges and you'll need to complete each of them yourself,
but of course, no worries.
We'll talk about solution of each challenge together.
If you want to become an expert in the game, please joins us now.
Now, if you would like it, I'll give you a sort of day money back guarantee.
So please enroll now and see you inside.
Good luck.